sixteenventures.com 2019-01-15

# Privacy Policy - Customer Success-driven Growth

This is our Privacy Policy for SixteenVentures.com

We Last Updated it on February 3, 2013

 _ **TL:DR**_ – At Sixteen Ventures, we are serious about protecting your online privacy and we’re gonna do everything in our power to keep your information private (since we worked so hard to get it in the first place!). However, if the feds ask for it, it’s theirs, man… you’re on your own. Also… stuff happens and if it gets out into the wild, sorry… it was an accident and we didn’t mean to but we also can’t be held responsible.

“I can’t be held responsible  
She was touching her face  
I won’t be held responsible  
She fell in love in the first place” – The Verve Pipe

Okay, so anyway… our Privacy Policy is here to explain our views and practices concerning privacy, and how they pertain to you.

Going forward the terms “You” or “Your” refers to, well, you as a participant in, or as a user of, the SixteenVentures .com website.

In the same vein, the terms “We” or “Our” or “Us” means Sixteen Ventures.

Furthermore, the terms “this site” or “this here site” or “our site” or anything like that means SixteenVentures.com.

Here’s a biggie… all information transmitted, emailed, Twittered, Facebooked, LinkedIn’d or otherwise submitted to SixteenVentures.com via this website or any of the things connected to this site shall be deemed to be the property of Sixteen Ventures and we (see above if you’re confused about who that’s referring to) are free to use such information for any act of good but no acts of evil.

Here’s another biggie… On this here site you will find links to other sites (as the web was intended to be used) but we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. Use your good judgement, cuz it’s out of our hands!

Oh yeah, and if the cops ask for anything about you, we totally reserve the right to release that information to law enforcement, the feds, the Illuminati, or whatever as we, in our sole and absolute discretion, deem necessary to comply with the law. The Dude – and Sixteen Ventures – abide.

## Section 1: Collected Information

 _ **TL:DR**_ – We collect tons of information on you as you navigate this here site. We do it. Everyone else does it. It’s a scene, man.

We automatically collect and/or track this stuff:

Web page http headers (home server domain names, IP address, type of client computer, and type of Web browser); information knowingly provided by you through on-line forms, registration forms, surveys, and/or other entries, such as email addresses, personal, financial or demographic information; information, user specific or aggregate, on what pages our visitors access; and E-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with Sixteen Ventures via e-mail.

## Section 2: Use of Data Collected

 _ **TL:DR**_ – We’re going to use the data we collect from you – either explicitly or through your actions – to advertise stuff to you so you’ll buy it. The theory is, the more specifically we target you the more likely you are to want what we’re selling and it won’t be incongruent with what you’re doing. At least its an ethos.

We use your personal, demographic and profile data to enhance your experience at our site and to enable us to present content we think you might be interested in.

We use your contact information to send you information about our company and promotional material from our partners. We may also use your personal, demographic and profile data to improve our site, for statistical analysis, for marketing and promotional purposes, and for editorial or feedback purposes for our advertisers. Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future telemarketing, SMS text-messaging, e-mails or postal mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and/or status of orders placed online.

Did you know that just by using this site, you agree that you may be contacted in any manner contemplated in this section even if your number is found on a do not call registry, in-house list or similar registry. Crazy, huh? But also pretty cool and hopefully effective.

## Section 3: Disclosure of Data to Third Parties

 _ **TL:DR**_ – If the man asks for your deets, and we think they’re onto something, we’ll squeal. If we think we can make money by doing a joint venture with someone or letting them contact you in exchange for a fee… we’re all over that. We’ll let other people look at the information we have on you, but only if they pay us… we’ll work diligently to prevent those who don’t pay us from accessing your info.

If you choose to provide personal information, it will be used for the following purposes:

considering you for a Sixteen Ventures product or service;  
as required by law; and  
for marketing products and services which we determine, in our sole judgment, that you might find of interest.

We reserve the right to share, rent, sell, or otherwise disclose data we collect to third parties. Any third party we share, rent, sell, or otherwise disclose data to will be prescreened by us, determined by us to be reputable, and will use the personal data for marketing products and services which we determine, in our sole judgment, that you might find of interest.

## Section 4: Your Opt-Out Rights

 _ **TL:DR**_ – You say the word and we won’t _ever_ contact you again, ever.

You may opt-out of receiving communications from us and/or our partners by not submitting your information.

We also allow you to remove your information from our marketing lists. If you remove your information from our marketing lists it will no longer be used by us to send promotional correspondence to you. You can remove your information from our marketing lists by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link at the bottom of every email we send you, or by sending your request, in writing, via email to: [info@sixteenventures.com](mailto:info@sixteenventures.com)

## Section 5: We Do Not Intend to Collect Data from Children

 _ **TL:DR**_ – Sixteen Ventures is a B2B consulting firm and we do business with other businesses and individuals in business; we do not do business with children under 18. Besides, no one under 18 should even be interested in what we do here and if they are they should go outside and play.

The information and services provided to us or our affiliates, sponsors, and advertisers are not intended to be viewed by children (under 18 years old). No information collected from children is knowingly used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside Sixteen Ventures.

No part of our web site is structured to attract anyone under the age of 18.

## Section 6: Our Right to Contact You

We reserve the right to contact you regarding your account status and changes to subscriber agreements, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to you.

## Section 7: Our Right to Change

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying you of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy or by posting the changes online at our site.

## Section 8: Our Contact Information

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us via email sent to: [info@sixteenventures.com](mailto:info@sixteenventures.com)

## Section 9: Anti Spam Policy. Can-Spam Act Compliance

 _ **TL:DR**_ – Guess what? We know the CAN-SPAM act better than you. We live it every day for our business, and the business of our clients. We don’t violate it… period.

Sixteen Ventures is dedicated to ensuring compliance with the ‘Can-Spam Act’, which took effect January 1, 2004. You may receive email from sixteenventures.com in the following circumstances:

  * Acknowledging your application has been received and requesting additional action
  * Requests for additional information to support your current application
  * Advertisements for third party products and services where we have determined that such product or service may be of interest to our customers
  * Response to your inquiries regarding the status of your transactional requests
  *  _ _Advertisements for our products, services, changes in services, new product availability__
  * Thanking you for your valued business

To ensure compliance with the Can-Spam Act, Sixteen Ventures has implemented the following guidelines for email delivery:

  * All emails sent to you by Sixteen Ventures will clearly identify Sixteen Ventures or Lincoln Murphy as the sender. FROM / SENDER: someone@sixteenventures.com or lincoln@lincolnmurphy.com (The actual sender will depend on the department it’s sent from, but all from addresses will end with @SixteenVentures.com or @LincolnMurphy.com).
  * The Subject Line of any email you receive will always accurately describe the subject matter of the email.
  * Any email from Sixteen Ventures will include the ability to unsubscribe from future email messages.
  * Unsubscribing will ensure the customer is removed from ALL lists at Sixteen Ventures; this excludes customer service emails regarding the processing and status of a current product.
  * All emails sent to you directly by Sixteen Ventures include valid postal address information in the footer.
  * All third party marketing partners are required to comply with the Can-Spam Act.
  * Emails sent to you directly by Sixteen Ventures will include an email address and physical address where you can send suggestions, complaints or other correspondence.

## Section 10: Information for ISPs

Web site: SixteenVentures.com  
Email Address: [info@sixteenventures.com](mailto:info@sixteenventures.com)

Sixteen Ventures understands consumers’ concerns over the use of their personal information.

We hope this information will aliviate any concerns you may have regarding our email policies. Sixteen Ventures and its affiliated sites use only an “opt-in or opt out” method of obtaining customer information, and it is not our policy or desire to send unsolicited email.

We obtain email addresses and personal information from third parties that follow the same set of policies.

Sixteen Ventures email messages always include information about the origin of the emails and instructions on how recipients can unsubscribe from receiving future email messages.

From time to time, Sixteen Ventures will enter into an arrangement with a third party website to allow individuals to opt into our marketing program on those third party websites. In each case the third party websites have represented and warranted to us, among other things,

  * that the data was collected voluntarily from individuals on website registrations and co-registrations,
  * that the sellers have a right, under any applicable privacy statements, to transfer the data to us, and
  * that SixteenVentures.com has the right to send marketing offers to the individuals.

We hope this information satisfies any questions or concerns you may have regarding the email practices of Sixten Ventures.

If you have additional questions or wish to discuss this matter further, please contact us at: [info@sixteenventures.com](mailto:info@sixteenventures.com)
